THE FOLLOWING CONTENT CONTAINS DEPICTIONS
OF CHILD MALTREATMENT.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
-[Aunt A] Heeju!
-[Sunok] Heeju!
-[Mija] Heeju!
-[Aunt B] Heeju, where are you?
-[Aunt B] Heeju!
-[Aunt A] Heeju! Heeju!
[Aunt A] Sunok, Sunok! Heeju!
[all speaking at once]
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
[women gasping]
How do we get down there?
[all gasping]
-[Mija] Heeju, it's me, Auntie Mija.
-I swear she's nothing but trouble.
[Mija] Right here!
[Aunt B] Are you okay?
-[Mija] How can we get her out of there?
-[Aunt B] What do we do?
[Sunok] You've got no idea how dangerous
this place is.
Fine then, go on.
Get back in there.
[Heeju] This woman is my mother.
"Nothing but bad luck."
That's what my mom always called me.
I thought my mom's misfortune
was because of me.
And so I always felt guilty.
At the time,
I didn't understand what that meant.
[9-Year-Old Heeju and Sunok crying]
[indistinct chatter]
[♪ melancholy music]
[Heeju] Spellbound by
the dazzling lights...
...people streamed endlessly
toward Gold Land.
[slot machines chiming and clicking]
They say not everything that glitters
is gold.
In the end,
it was nothing more than a gilded grave.
Maybe my mother was dazzled
by those lights, too,
wagering everything she had.
[Croupier] Player, banker.
[Heeju] Hoping for
a single stroke of luck.
Unfortunately, luck is never fair, is it?
[Croupier] Final bets.
-Ah.
-[Croupier] Out.
-[Sunok grunts]
-[Croupier] You fold?
-House wins.
-[Sunok] I can't believe this.
-[man groans]
-[Sunok exhales sharply]
[bus engine rumbling]
13, JEONGSAN BUS TERMINAL
SEOKWOL-DONG
[brakes hissing]
[door closes]
Did you eat yet?
Ramyeon.
[bag rustling]
[food crunching]
I wanna go to school, Mom.
Da In gets to go to school
and she's a year younger than me.
You can go next year.
Not here, though.
You can go in Seoul.
Really?
Yes. Really.
[exhales]
I just can't live in
this place any longer.
STYLE
::cue()
We'll go to Seoul.
[crunching]
[Heeju] As always, it was just a lie.
But even if it was a lie,
I wanted to believe it.
THE CITY OF DREAMS AND HOPE
WELCOME TO GOLD LAND
HIGH-VALUE LOANS, HAENGBOK PAWNSHOP
LENDING, PURCHASING
GOLD, SILVER, JEWELRY, WATCHES
TOP PRICES PAID FOR GOLD
-[Cheoljung] Come here.
-[Heeju] Instead of leaving like she said,
my mother got married
to the pawnshop owner.
On the condition
that he paid off her debt.
Both me and my mother
were like collateral at his shop.
[clock loudly echoing]
[Sunok] I said cut it out.
[Man on Street] Slow down.
Be careful, kids.
[children laughing and shouting]
[Heeju] A heart with no destination
to go always lets the feet know first.
For many years I was stuck,
walking down a road I never wanted
to return to.
I prayed every day that my destination
would be somewhere else.
In reality, the dream
that felt so far away
only grew closer and more familiar.
[Male Singer] ♪ All the things
I thought I could be ♪
♪ Wild and free ♪
♪ Leave it all behind ♪
♪ As you fall in line ♪
♪ I'm not expecting any laughter ♪
♪ There's nothing left ♪
♪ Just the pieces of everything
we could have been before ♪
♪ Evermore ♪
♪ I don't feel it like I used to ♪
♪ Anymore ♪
[Heeju] My mother was like a plant
that could no longer bloom,
slowly withering away.
The thought that I could end up
like her...
...It terrified me.
[Male Singer] ♪ Still calling through
the night ♪
♪ I leave behind all of the seasons... ♪
[Heeju] At Haengbok Pawnshop,
there is no happiness.
Only someone's collateral,
held like hostages.
[distant jet engine roaring]
[Heeju] If only I could
fly somewhere else.
How nice would it be?
Anywhere.
Anywhere but here.
[Male Singer] ♪ On your own ♪
[Heeju] Sometimes in the evenings,
the pawnshop became
a gambling den.
[indistinct chatter]
Soju there, cigarettes here.
We have to sell it all.
[Man in Pawnshop A] Bring it here!
[exhales sharply]
STYLE
::cue()
[exhales]
[locker and chains rattle]
[chains rattling]
[lock clicks]
[lock clicking]
[gasps]
[chains clinking]
[lock squeaking]
[door opens]
[locker creaks]
[Man in Pawnshop B] Mr. Han.
I said I'd give it to you by next week!
[Cheoljung] So you keep saying.
[Cheoljung] I trust money, not words.
[Cheoljung] People say they'll
pay back billions, even trillions.
[whimpering]
[crying]
What's wrong?
Is your little heart pounding?
I could cut you open
for screwing me out of my money.
[Cheoljung] Is that what
you're worried about?
[whimpers]
[Cheoljung] Look here.
You see that?
It's easy to control
it when it's my own flesh.
[Cheoljung] But on someone else's,
not so much.
That's why I always cut myself first
to show you.
[muffled wailing]
[gasps]
[panicked breathing]
[lock clicks]
[gasps]
[door lock beeping]
[door creaks open]
What are you doing here?
Just my homework.
[Heeju] I guess I fell asleep.
Oh, really?
[Heeju gasps]
[panicked breathing]
[whimpering]
STYLE
::cue()
-[Heeju screams]
-[Cheoljung grunts]
[gasps]
-[Heeju screams]
-[wailing]
-[Cheoljung groaning]
-[panicked breathing]
[Cheoljung] Heeju!
[pained groaning]
[breathing heavily]
-[Sunok] Where are you?
-[Heeju] I'm leaving this place.
I won't go back. That man is crazy.
He's not even human. I'm too scared to.
[Sunok] Where else would you go?
Anywhere. I don't know.
[Sunok] You got any money?
How are you gonna survive on your own?
I don't know.
I'll figure it out.
And you?
You're okay living like this?
You actually think he sees me
as his niece?
[Sunok] Go and stay with Mija for a while.
When your uncle cools off,
you can come back.
[groaning]
No, Mom, why can't we
just leave this place?
[Sunok] Don't call me Mom.
[phone receiver clicks]
[Heeju] Oh, that's right.
I don't have a mother.
I almost forgot.
I'm nothing but an utterly luckless brat.
[phone receiver rattles]
[Heeju crying]
[crying continues]
[♪ sad music]
[♪ music continues]
EPISODE 2
HOMECOMING
[exhales]
[phone trilling]
[exhales sharply]
Uh, hi there.
Last night there was a car accident on
National Route 6 around midnight, I think.
Have there been any reports
of the accident yet?
STYLE
::cue()
[inhales and exhales sharply]
Could you tell me what hospital he's in?
[Female Police Officer] May I have
the name of the person calling?
I...
[shudders]
[phone beeps]
[exhales]
[breathes heavily]
[gasps]
[Heeju] There isn't?
Okay, thank you.
[phone beeps]
[phone chimes]
[trilling]
[inhales sharply]
Hello.
I'm calling to check on a patient who
was brought to the ER after
a car accident around midnight last night.
It's a man...
[Female Security Officer] Hey, Heeju!
Heeju!
They want all of us in the office.
Why?
[Female Security Officer] The police
are here now.
They have some questions for all of us.
[Female Security Officer] Ms. Cha, too.
We gotta go.
Sure.
[door opens]
[mouse button clicks]
[Male Detective A] What is that?
That can't be normal, can it?
Yesterday, who was-who was in charge
of the scanner?
Uh, I was.
The warning alarm went off, right?
Aren't you supposed to request
a physical inspection from customs?
Uh, sir, well...
She reported it to me.
As the one in charge, I review
all anomalies and make the final call.
A visual inspection by an expert
is considered the most accurate method.
The alarms are always going off.
And for inbound cargo,
physical inspections
are deemed unnecessary unless
it's an emergency.
This is because it's already been through
a thorough screening
at the outbound checkpoint,
especially when transporting a casket
with a dead body.
[Male Detective A exhales sharply]
[sighs]
So what kind of goods
were they supposedly smuggling?
Ma'am, we never said anything
about smuggling.
The police wouldn't be making such
a fuss if it was for anything else.
[Male Detective B]
Look, you all know this man, right?
San Air first officer Lee Dokyung.
Yeah, I've seen him around a few times.
[Male Detective B] Have you been
in touch recently?
Maybe the last few days?
[Yujin] No.
[Male Detective B]
What about everyone else?
This airport's tiny, so,
weird no one knows him.
Are you asking about the captain because
he's somehow connected to all this?
No, not quite.
It's not like that.
Oh.
Heeju, you were working
at the arrivals terminal.
You must know him.
You would have handled security
for inbound crew.
Yeah.
[cell phone vibrates]
[Male Detective B] I see.
Have you been in contact recently?
Well, it's not like we keep in touch
or anything like that.
We just say hello when
he went through security.
Understood.
-It's Dokyung. They found him.
-Well, where is he?
[Detective Kang]
He's at Yangpo Jeil Hospital.
[Male Detective A] All right,
thanks everyone.
We'll be in touch.
Heeju, wait a minute.
Can I speak with you?
[machines beeping and hissing]
[Male Doctor] Prep the patient
for surgery.
[Nurses] Yes, Doctor.
STYLE
::cue()
[Yujin] So how long have you been close
with Lee Dokyung?
[Heeju] What?
This isn't your first time, is it?
Smuggling goods.
Uh, Ms. Cha, I'm not sure exactly
what you're trying to say.
[Yujin] Fine.
First time or not,
keep your mouth shut
and pretend you don't know anything.
If you're caught by the police,
you understand you and I are both done?
[exhales]
Send me your resignation letter tonight.
And don't come into work tomorrow.
[Yujin] I'll talk to the company
and sort things out.
Once the police wrap up
their investigation,
someone will have to take the fall.
[Yujin] I don't know what's going on
between you two,
but our best hope...
...Is that Lee Dokyung goes and dies.
[inhales and exhales deeply]
[car approaching]
[Female Nurse C] Is Mr. Lee Dokyung's
guardian here?
[Hocheol] Here.
[Female Nurse C] Looks like
the surgery went well.
Mr. Lee is now in recovery.
He's in room 3103.
Is he awake yet?
[Female Nurse C] Uh...
[screaming]
[Female Nurse C]
It usually takes about an hour
or two for the anesthesia to wear off,
so he's still asleep.
You can't see him yet.
Sir, he still needs to rest!
[clock ticking rapidly]
[distant keyboard clacking]
[door creaking]
[gasps]
[panicked breathing]
[cell phone vibrates]
[Detective Kang] Yeah.
[Detective Kang] Yeah, I'll head down
to the first floor.
Okay.
[exhales]
[gasping]
Dokyung.
Wake up.
It's me, Heeju.
Dokyung, can you hear me?
[Heeju breathing erratically]
[Heeju] Dokyung.
[groans]
[Heeju] Dokyung, can you hear me?
[labored breathing]
-[Dokyung] Heeju.
-[exhales sharply]
[Dokyung] I told you not to come here,
didn't I?
I said I'd contact you.
It's okay.
I managed to sneak in.
[exhales]
And the van?
Don't worry. I hid it.
Somewhere no one will know.
-Where's that?
-[Heeju] In Jeongsan,
in the abandoned mines.
STYLE
::cue()
I left it deep in the tunnels
where no one goes anymore.
-[groans]
-[exhales]
[pained groaning]
You did it.
You did it, Heeju.
I'll take care of everything from here.
You should go now.
I'm okay. You can go.
The police came to the airport today.
The police? Why?
Well, it looks like they think you were
involved in smuggling in that casket,
and they also know you're in the hospital
because of a car accident. Also...
...those men who hit you with the car,
they're here waiting for you.
I saw them.
[exhales sharply]
[Heeju] Let's turn ourselves in.
If we confess to the police now,
the charges might not be that bad.
The police aren't the problem, Heeju.
It's the men you saw outside.
If I were to tell the police
where their drugs are located...
-...Those guys would...
-But it's not drugs.
What?
That's not what's in the casket.
It's not drugs at all.
[gasps]
Then what is it?
Gold bars.
There are a whole bunch of gold bars
that say 10 kilograms on them.
[Heeju] I didn't count,
but there has to be 100.
100 ten-kilogram gold bars?
You're positive?
-[Dokyung] Did you see them yourself?
-Yeah.
Wait a minute.
You mean-you mean there's a ton of gold?
But we should just return it.
If they'll go this far to get it,
then you should just give
it back to them, right?
We can tell the police that you didn't
know what was in the casket because
you really didn't know, right?
No, Heeju.
Wait, wait, wait, Heeju.
Wait a minute.
[Dokyung] So you're completely sure no one
knows that you hid the van in the mines?
[bus engine rumbling]
JEONGSAN BUS TERMINAL
[♪ tense music]
[Dokyung] Heeju.
Don't tell anyone where the casket is.
No one but the two of us can know.
I won't tell anyone, either.
I swear I'll keep it a secret.
No matter what.
Even with a knife to my throat.
[bus engine rumbling]
[brakes hissing]
[bus engine revving]
[birds chirping]
[Dokyung] From now on,
this is our whole lives.
[Dokyung] I'm gonna turn myself in.
If the police can't find the gold bars...
...I could get out in a year.
[Dokyung] With a good lawyer I could
even get a suspended sentence.
You're gonna have to keep
the gold safe for us, Heeju.
Until I can get out.
STYLE
::cue()
[Heeju breathing heavily]
[groans]
[exhales sharply]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[exhales]
DAD! BE SAFE AGAIN TODAY
[car trunk opening]
[exhales]
[Dokyung] First, bury the gold bars
in the mine...
...so that if anyone goes in,
they won't see them.
[zipper unzipping]
[water dripping]
Move them one at a time.
I know you can do it.
[Dokyung] It will take a while.
[grunts]
[Dokyung] But please bury them.
[gold bar clinks]
[Heeju grunts]
[grunting]
[water dripping continues]
[gold bar clangs]
[Heeju groans]
[lighter flicks]
[Dokyung] Take the van back
to the abandoned warehouse.
The one from that night.
[bottle spritzing]
[Dokyung] Make sure you don't
leave fingerprints or anything.
That way even if the police find the van,
it won't matter.
They can't trace it to you.
[Dokyung] Find a place
to lay low for a while.
Don't try to contact me.
Don't even look for me.
[Dokyung] I will find a way
to contact you if it's necessary.
[Hocheol] Hey, Captain.
STYLE
::cue()
It's me, Park.
[metal chair clanking]
[Hocheol] Ah, open your eyes.
I know you're awake.
[wincing]
[panicked breathing]
You look like you're gonna piss yourself.
How did a little bitch
like you pull this off?
[Hocheol] Why'd you do it?
You upset?
Did I somehow upset you?
[Hocheol] Up until now,
we always got along.
You that desperate for cash?
[Hocheol] Money always screws things up.
I understand.
Well, I guess I'm
the one who put you here,
so I'm partly to blame.
[Hocheol] Let's go back
to the original deal.
The casket for 200 million.
Ah, it's fine.
You don't need to say anything.
[panicked breathing]
[Hocheol] This is your phone, right?
[Hocheol] Your partner,
the one who took off with the van?
Call him.
Found his burner phone.
The real one.
Now, which is it?
[Hocheol] Huh?
All you need is a finger.
Just press it, you little...
You really expect me to trust you?
You might kill me after I return
the casket.
[Dokyung] You already tried to
kill me once.
[Hocheol] Yeah, I know.
Why did I do that?
Deposit one billion won into my account.
Get all these cops off my tail.
And get me out of the country.
Then I'll tell you where the casket is.
Like I can trust you.
[exhales sharply]
I've got nothin' to tell you, then.
Okay.
[Hocheol] Heard you got 22 stitches.
[Hocheol] Let's open 'em up!
[muffled shouting]
Just one fucking phone call
and this'd be over.
You should have called when I
was being nice, you stupid fuck!
[groaning]
-[grunting]
-[Detective Kang] Sir!
[muffled groaning]
[breathing heavily]
Better take care of yourself.
I'll be back soon, Captain.
[breathing heavily]
[crickets chirping]
HAENGBOK PAWNSHOP
[door squeaking]
[Sunok] We're closed.
[Sunok] What's going on?
What are you doing here?
I'm just gonna stay here for a little.
A few days.
Well, maybe a month.
What about work?
I quit, so it'll only be until
I find something else.
STYLE
::cue()
Don't worry. It won't be long.
You said you'd never come back.
[Sunok] Guess you found out the real world
isn't so easy, huh?
[Sunok scoffs]
That's what life is like for women
with nothing to offer but their body.
I didn't live like you did, Auntie.
Then why'd you crawl back here?
You say it's temporary but you can't
even afford a hotel?
And what about you?
Are you still living with
a man who beats you?
[exhales]
Forget it.
I'll get a hotel.
[Sunok] If it's really only
for a little while,
you can stay here.
I said you can stay.
Have you eaten?
It's fine.
I'll take care of myself.
I'll just come back here to sleep.
Is that, uh, gambling den still here?
Nope. We had to stop.
We got raided, so...
-Then what is he up to now?
-I don't know.
He barely comes home these days.
That's a good thing.
I don't want him to know I'm here.
Don't tell anyone else, either.
No one around here
is asking about you.
Where are you going?
I'm getting sheets for you.
You're gonna have to sleep in the vault.
[Sunok] The latch is broken,
so make sure you lock the front door.
[Sunok] Oh, look at you.
[Sunok] The bags under your eyes
look awful.
And what's on your hands?
What the hell have you been doing?
Oh, forget it.
[sink turns on]
[water running]
[exhales sharply]
[Dokyung] When this goes to court,
I'll need an expensive lawyer.
And money for bail.
GOLD BAR
We can sell one gold bar
and use that to cover expenses.
Okay, how?
There must be a way to do it.
[Dokyung] See what you can find out.
I'll look into it, too.
HOW TO BUY AND SELL
A 75-GRAM GOLD BAR?
WHAT IS A 75-GRAM GOLD BAR?
[Dokyung] Heeju.
When I get out of prison,
the first thing we'll do is sell all
the gold bars and get outta here.
Maybe France or wherever.
[Dokyung] Somewhere no one
will ever find us.
This is a once in a lifetime opportunity
for us, Heeju.
It could completely change our lives.
You can do this.
[gold bar clinks]
[♪ suspenseful music]
STYLE
::cue()
[Investigating Officer A]
Have you ever seen this van before, sir?
No, I've never seen it before.
There's no van like that
in the neighborhood,
so I have no idea how it got there.
[Investigating Officer A]
Do you have any injuries?
[Witness] I mean, I'm not hurt anywhere.
But look at this.
When I got here,
everything was a mess.
It looks like someone crashed
and left the van here.
We found the van, sir,
with the 9900 plate.
[Investigating Officer B] Casket?
There's no casket here.
-What do you wanna eat?
-I dunno.
Ah, shit.
[phone beeps]
[Male Detective A] I'm starving.
They found the van,
but the casket's not in there.
Lee Dokyung keeps denying
that he knows anything about it.
-For now, at least.
-[Hocheol] Good work.
Come to the hotel soon.
We'll grab food.
[phone beeps]
[inhales]
All the men we sent to the airport,
you picked them out yourself, right?
Yeah.
You specifically told me to pick out
the smartest and strongest.
Lee Dokyung didn't act on his own.
[exhales]
There's someone else.
Ah!
I already told you,
it's not one of my boys!
[Gitae] I think...
[door opens]
You wanted to see me?
[Hocheol inhales on cigarette]
Hand over your phone.
You gotta unlock it.
[Hocheol] Where'd you hide the casket?
What?
You were the one who drove the van
from Yangpo Airport.
Uh, I already told my boss all about it.
That shit head pilot.
Uh, Lee Dokyung, he...
...he pulled out a gun
and held it to my head.
He took off with the van.
But that night, the first person
to find our missing van was you.
You.
[Hocheol] And you were the only one
who saw the driver's face.
Aren't you gonna tell me who it was?
Uh, yeah, I mean...
I did my best to try and get
a good look.
It-it was just so dark, though.
Yeah, and the casket?
[Woogy] Sir.
I don't know.
I-I swear it wasn't me.
I-I passed out yesterday 'cause I
was all beat up.
[phone clatters on floor]
-[grunts]
-[pained groaning]
Hey, boss. This isn't right.
Get your fucking hands off.
-[grunts]
-[Woogy groaning]
I already know everything
so either confess or lose an ear.
Sir, I dunno. I promise.
I'm telling the truth.
I swear I'm telling you...
Lee Dokyung already told the police
you helped him,
so just tell me where it is!
[Woogy whimpers]
[Hocheol] This is your last chance
to confess, you asshole!
[Gitae] You serious?
Woogy, you shit.
You tell him where it is now!
No, I don't know anything! Ah!
[Woogy shouting]
Please don't kill me! Please!
[grunts]
[Woogy whimpering]
Get the fuck out of my sight.
-[whimpering]
-[Hocheol] Fuck!
[kicks phone]
[groans]
[Woogy] I'll get going, sir.
STYLE
::cue()
[exhales sharply]
[door closes]
[Gitae] It's not him?
Well, what the hell was that all about,
then?
Lee Dokyung did have an accomplice,
and that person hid the casket.
I had to make sure that
it wasn't one of our guys.
[exhales sharply]
What are you gonna do?
[Hocheol scoffs]
Seems like finding the casket
isn't even our biggest problem.
[exhales sharply]
Does the chairman know?
[exhales]
[sighs]
-I'm sorry.
-[exhales]
Must be really tough on you.
[Gitae] Didn't he say once he wraps up
in Cambodia and returns to Gold Land,
he'd hand over the hotel
and everything else to you?
[Gitae] You really should do your best not
to upset him right now.
[Hocheol] Fucker!
You need to shut it.
[exhales angrily]
You can murder just about anyone.
The chairman will forgive you for that,
but if you lose his money...
That's a different story.
[Gitae] What are you gonna do?
[Gitae] He'll be coming back soon.
[locker doors banging]
[pills rattling]
[wound squelches]
[door creaks open]
Come on in.
Hmm.
Are you here to sell?
Oh. I'm guessing you don't recognize me.
[Woogy] I used to live in Bukju, too.
The old mining town there.
No?
Really?
[Woogy] Everyone tells me I look
just like when I was a kid.
[Woogy exhales sharply]
I guess you don't remember.
[Woogy] So, tell me.
Is Heeju with you?
[Woogy] I heard she went to Seoul
a while ago, but is she back now?
She's not.
Oh, she's not? Hmm.
Thought I saw her.
[laughs]
Heeju's not here.
I doubt she's ever coming back.
[Sunok] So pawn something or get out.
Yeah, sure. Got a business to run.
[chuckles]
[Woogy exhales]
[Woogy] See ya!
[door creaks shut]
STYLE
::cue()
[truck engine rumbling]
DONGHWA JEWELRY
[Male Jewelry Store Owner]
Did you say a 10-kilogram gold bar?
Uh, I don't really have anything that big.
There's not really a market for that.
[Male Jewelry Store Owner]
I mean, I guess if someone
really wanted one,
it could be made to order, but...
-How much would it cost?
-[Male Jewelry Store Owner] Right now?
With our economy the way it is,
the current price of gold is pretty high.
[Male Jewelry Store Owner]
A kilo could go up to 150 million,
so ten kilos is 1.5 billion.
[inhales sharply]
Mm.
So, how much...
...do you think someone would be able
to sell it for?
Well, first I gotta make sure
it's pure gold.
So I'd need to get a look at it.
If it is pure, then I'd consider
offering 1.3 or 4 billion.
I know, market price is higher than that.
[Male Jewelry Store Owner]
Are you saying you have a 10-kilogram bar
of pure gold you're looking to sell?
Uh, no, I don't.
Just curious.
Just go.
You're wasting my time, young lady.
BEER, LIQUOR, MIJA
[rustling]
Who is it?
[grunts]
Hold on.
I haven't even opened yet.
[grunts]
[Mija] Heeju?
Wh-what are you doing here?
[chuckles]
Auntie, how are you?
Oh, same old, same old!
This way. Oh!
[Mija] Look at you. Sit down!
[chuckles]
Excuse the mess.
I was just eating.
Have you eaten yet?
Yeah.
Oh, it's been so long.
When'd you come back?
You here to stay?
No, just here a little while.
[Mija] You brat.
You never even called me once.
I'm sorry, Auntie.
I was busy trying to make a living.
Yeah, of course you were.
[sniffles]
So how are you really doing?
Well...
...would you...
...could you maybe lend me some money?
How much you need?
It's kind of a lot.
50 million won or so.
I could pay it back really quickly,
though.
I'll have it in a month or so.
[Mija] Things haven't been easy for you,
either, have they?
[whimpers]
Of course you need money.
Sunok's cancer,
I know all about it.
[Mija] I mean, I tried to get her
to go to the hospital, but she won't go.
She said she can barely afford food
for herself.
[Mija] I don't even think
your uncle knows.
Not that he'd care.
Shit, he barely treats her like a person.
Oh, it pisses me off.
[crying]
I know.
I know all her medical bills would be
about 50 million won.
[Mija] Hospital, treatments, operation.
[Mija exhales]
[Mija sniffles]
[Mija] I don't have that kind of money.
I live paycheck to paycheck, too.
I've got nothing.
[exhales]
-[Woogy] Hey, Heeju!
-[gasps]
Is that you?
[Woogy laughs]
It is you!
Long time, no see!
It's me, Woogy.
We both lived in that mining town
when we were kids.
Sorry, I don't really...
Sure you do. I was the kid with
the bald spot right here.
What'cha doin'?
[Woogy] You buyin' somethin'?
A ring?
I can get you a good deal.
Ah, damn.
It's been so long, right?
We went to, uh, elementary school together
so it's been...
...over ten years now?
STYLE
::cue()
[exhales sharply]
Okay, how 'bout Chan?
Or Seonghun? You know, the kid who
followed you 'cause he liked you.
No, I don't.
Sorry, I don't remember.
Well, that hurt my feelings a little.
Hey, you really don't remember?
'Cause I remember you.
Wait, wait!
What about freeze tag?
We used to always play
after school together.
I'd get tagged and you'd unfreeze me.
Maybe this'll jog your memory!
Freeze!
[exhales sharply]
[breathing heavily]
[Heeju wails]
[bus door squeaks]
[exhales sharply]
[knocking]
[gasps]
I'll see you around!
[whimpers]
[glass cracking]
[screams]
[panicked breathing]
[Heeju screams]
[breathing heavily]
HAENGBOK PAWNSHOP
[Mr. Jang grunts]
'Kay, let me see.
[inhales sharply]
[groans]
[Mr. Jang] Yeah, this is real.
How-how much you give for it?
You don't need to know that.
And they never came back for it?
It's been over three months.
It's been over three months. Hmm.
[Mr. Jang] I'll give you 25 million.
-We'll say 30 mill on the receipt, though.
-[Sunok] Mr. Jang.
All these years we've been doing business
and that's the best you can do?
I'm being generous here.
Collateral isn't worth market price.
Just pay for the gold ring and get out.
I can find someone else
on my own for this.
[Mr. Jang] All right, all right!
All right.
All right, all right.
I'll do it.
[Mr. Jang] I'll give you 27.
[inhales deeply]
You understand I need
to make money, too.
30 million.
[inhales]
Someone else already offered me 35.
Okay, all right.
I'll pay you tomorrow.
You drive a hard bargain.
[groaning]
Ah, shit.
Fucking bitch.
[snorts, spits]
[humming]
Mr. Jang, wait.
Who are you?
I heard you trade in gold.
Do you?
[Mr. Jang] Yeah, I do.
Which pawn shop are you with?
Don't think we've met yet.
If the piece is really big,
would you still buy it?
Cast gold,
or something like a golden pig?
[inhales]
A bar. A gold bar.
A gold bar?
Is it pure? How heavy?
Ten?
I'll buy it.
[Mr. Jang] I'd need to see it.
How 'bout you get in the car.
Show me and we'll talk.
No.
Uh, could you just give me
an estimate, please?
Sure. It's 580 won for 3.75 grams.
[Mr. Jang] So ten of those is 5.8 mil,
but that's only if this whole thing
is above board.
I guess since you came to me,
you can't sell it at
a regular jewelry store.
[Mr. Jang] Am I right?
My company, we can make a deal for 10.
100, even.
If you're serious about selling
this thing, hop in. Then let's...
Uh, I don't...
I'll think about it a little more.
You can't just bring this up
and then leave.
At least let me have a look at it.
-Let's see it.
-What?
[Mr. Jang] Is it in the bag here?
-I told you I'd give you a good deal!
-Let go!
[Heeju] Stop it!
[both shouting]
[Mr. Jang] Ah, fuck, that stings!
[groans]
Why is everyone such
a fucking bitch today?
[groans]
STYLE
::cue()
[breathing heavily]
[Sunok] Where the hell have you been?
[Sunok] Someone came asking
for you this morning. Some guy.
Who was it?
No idea.
That's why I'm asking.
[Sunok] He said he lived in
the same town as us,
but I don't recognize him.
He seemed shady.
Like one of those thugs who collect money
for loan sharks.
-[Sunok] Did you borrow money?
-[exhales sharply]
Tell me you haven't been gambling.
No, I'm not like you.
I would never.
[Sunok inhales]
[sips]
[pill bottle rattles]
TYLENOL
What are you, sick?
Have you been in pain?
Doesn't matter.
[exhales sharply]
It's cancer, isn't it?
Mija told you.
Why didn't you tell me?
You ran away 'cause you hate me.
Then at least listen to Mija when
she tells you to go to the doctor.
[Sunok] I did.
I did go.
Doctor said it was bone cancer
or something.
[exhales]
[Heeju] Then we have to go back.
Go back so we can find out
what stage it is,
what treatments there are,
if you need surgery.
Are you sitting around here like
an idiot just because of money?
What's with you?
[exhales sharply]
We're going to the hospital tomorrow.
I don't even have money for food.
We'll figure out a way to make
the money later.
[Sunok] Oh, is that how it works?
If life were that easy,
why are we here?
[Sunok] I've looked into
it more than enough.
The doctors said I
was better off not knowing.
The surgery might get me
a few more years.
Or I could die now.
What's the difference?
We're all gonna die anyway.
Oh, I'm tired of living like this.
[exhales]
Come on.
You don't really mean that, do you?
We're going to the doctor tomorrow.
Just let it go.
You want me to call an ambulance?
I'm taking you one way or another.
Be sure to lock the door
when you go to sleep.
But...
[groans]
[door creaking]
[exhales]
STYLE
::cue()
[crickets chirping]
HAENGBOK PAWNSHOP
[car engine shuts off]
[exhales]
[glove compartment opens]
[electricity quietly buzzing]
[door creaking]
[door clangs]
[distant rattling]
[door creaks quietly]
[door creaking]
[door knob clicking]
[breathing erratically]
-[Heeju] Who are you?
-Holy fuck, you scared me.
You gotta be kidding.
Everyone's walkin' around
with a gun lately.
You know that shit's illegal, right?
Get out or I'll scream.
This isn't Seoul, Heeju.
You think anyone will come for you?
I already called the police.
[Woogy] Bullshit.
The police?
You really want that?
[gun rattling]
We met a few days ago.
[Woogy] And I almost fucking died.
[exhales sharply]
[Woogy] The person in the van.
It was you.
At first I wasn't so sure.
But when I saw you on the street,
I knew.
Don't act like you know me.
You're not my friend.
[exhales sharply]
Don't change the subject.
Where's the casket?
We found the van back at the warehouse.
[Woogy] But the casket was missing.
Tell me where it is.
[shuddering]
[Woogy] Ah.
That it?
[Heeju] Stay right there!
I'm not afraid to shoot you.
You sure it's loaded?
You can find anything at a pawn shop.
Do you really want to find out?
Okay, okay.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
But just think for a sec.
[Woogy] That stuff in the casket.
The drugs.
Come on.
[Woogy] Do you even know how to sell it?
You can't do it alone.
Lee Dokyung's basically crippled
after his accident.
What good are the drugs to you, huh?
[Woogy] If you can't sell 'em,
they're useless.
-Heeju...
-[Heeju] I said don't move!
I came here to help you out, Heeju.
[Woogy] If I wanted to hurt you,
I would have brought the others.
Let's just talk, yeah?
Don't-don't move!
I swear I'll shoot you!
Put the gun down.
I told you to stay!
[whimpers]
[Heeju groaning]
[Woogy] Ah, shit.
[gun cocks]
I knew it.
You're a fuckin' liar.
-Holy shit!
-[Heeju] No, wait.
[Heeju grunting]
[screams]
[clattering]
[Heeju whimpers]
Look, I tried to be nice, but shit.
I'll fucking shank you,
so stay down.
STYLE
::cue()
[groans]
Why the fuck is this thing so heavy?
[bag thumping]
[Heeju groaning]
[Woogy grunting]
[gold bars clink]
[breathing heavily]
[Woogy] Oh, fuck.
Heeju.
What is this?
[Heeju breathing heavily]
[♪ tense music]
[♪ music continues]